

Fábio Rodrigues

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

910179878

ffrr.rodrigues@gmail.com

Skills

Java

JavaScript + AJAX + JQuery

SQL / mySQL / Hibernate

HTML & CSS

Spring EE / Spring MVC

Git (agile)

Maven + Tomcat + ANT

Linux/Unix/MacOS/Windows

ThymeLeaf/JSP/PHP

Web Development

Functional Programming

Object Oriented Programming

JUnit

Design Patterns

Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Github

MyWebsite

Languages

English

Portuguese

Hobbies

Travelling, listening to and playing music, documenting and photographing older medieval towns throughout Europe.

Profile

After working 2 years as a QA tester, I knew that my next big step was in software development. When the opportunity to jump-start my career and become a dev came to be, I took it without skipping a beat! Programming went from hobby to field of study really quick and it has become my everyday. When I'm not programming, I'm thinking about what sort of programming project I want to be associated with next.

Employment History

QA Tester (T2), Intuit, Porto

OCTOBER 2018 - OCTOBER 2020

- · QA Tester, functional testing;
- · Ticket based documentation, JIRA, Salesforce;
- · Internal escalation through different product / bug teams;
- · Back-office support;
- · Customer engagement;

Customer Support, Concentrix, Porto

JANUARY 2015 - AUGUST 2018

- · Troubleshooting and fixing product software issues;
- · Account security;
- · Management of team staff and affairs.
- · Mentored new hires on apple products and how to troubleshoot;

Education

Academia de Código, Porto

JANUARY 2021 - APRIL 2021

Intensive course in software development. Junior Full Stack Developer

FormaBase, Porto

OCTOBER 2020 - JANUARY 2021

WebDeveloper Course. 130h

ISEP, Porto

JUNE 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2020

Advanced Mathematics course. 300h

12º, Conservatório de Música da Jobra, Albergaria-a-Velha

SEPTEMBER 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2018

Degree in jazz music - guitar;

Extra-curricular activities

Music Teacher - Jazz, Freelancer, Porto

JANUARY 2015 - OCTOBER 2020

I am continuously involved with music students and music projects as I give individual and group lessons.

